The monitors are humming in the artificial
light
I've been staring at the ceiling through a
never-ending night
I can't feel the floor beneath me, the gravity is
gone
Just a broken piece of metal, waiting for the
dawn
But I turn my heavy head and look across the room
You're sleeping in the corner, a beacon in the
gloom You didn't take the transport, you didn't
fly away You planted down your boots and swore
that you would stay The structural integrity's
completely compromised But I can see the
sanctuary reflecting in your eyes You cross the
silent ward and you pull me to your chest Holding
down the armor so the engine gets to rest You are
the anchor's hold Keeping me from drifting out
into the cold When the orbit was broken When the
vessel was wrecked You wrapped your arms around
The damage to protect A gravitational embrace
In the middle of the dark Holding all the pieces
Saving the spark I'm surviving the crash
Because you wouldn't let me go You are the
anchor's hope
They're running the diagnostics, reading out
the chart. They can fix the heavy machinery, but
they cannot
fix the heart. I
was terrified of floating into the endless
black, a ghost inside a machine that is never
You're coming back
But you're standing by the console, your hands
upon the glass Refusing every order to let the
moment pass You pull me in again, tighter than
before We're fighting off the vacuum right here
on the floor The structural integrity's
completely compromised But I can see the
sanctuary reflecting in your eyes You cross the
silent ward and you pull me to your chest Holding
down the armor so the engine gets to rest
You are the anchors hold Keeping me from
drifting out into the cold When the orbit was
broken, when the vessel was wrecked You wrapped
your arms around the damage to protect A
gravitational embrace in the middle of the dark
Holding all the pieces, saving the spark. I'm
surviving the crash because you wouldn't let me
go. You are the anchor's host.
I can't
feel my legs I can't feel the ground But I can feel
your arms And I am safe and sound Are the anchors
whole? Keeping me from drifting out into the
cold When the orbit was broken, when the vessel
was wrecked You wrapped your arms around the
damage to protect A gravitational embrace in
the middle of the dark Holding all the pieces,
saving the spark I'm surviving the crash
because you wouldn't let me go You are the
anchor's hold Never
let me go The gravitational embrace
Holding me in place